Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
We are in the presence of my Sheik.
I don't want to...
cause a trouble.
What were you doing with...
that ring?
If you had this the whole time...
why didn't you tell me?
I have answers...
Osman Bey.
We'll talk in somewhere else.
Forgive me my Sheik.
My Beys...
you were not invited to...
have greater troubles, and
become hostile to each other.
Don't worry my Sheik.
But...
if you allow, I don't want to cause
a disturbance.
Then, let it happen.
Renew your fellowship.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, the compassionate, the merciful)
The arrow which aimed potter Idris...
shot Osman Bey, Kumral Abdal.
Osman Bey can remove that arrow from
his chest, my Sheik.
But I don't know if he can stop the blood.
- Is Osman Bey inside?
- He is, Dündar Bey.
Umur Bey, now tell me.
Where did you find this ring?
My daughter found this ring.
How?
She found it while chasing the betrayer
who killed potter Idris.
We followed the tracks.
They led us nowhere.
Malhun Hatun, tell me.
Is there anything we miss?
No Osman Bey.
When I asked her...
She didn't tell me...
while she has the ring, huh?
Why did you hide this from me?
It was obvious that the owner of the ring
was not a random man, but a Bey.
I didn't want to put both you and her
in a difficult situation...
before finding out what's happening.
What are you talking about Umur Bey?
Do you know how many martyres...
I gave, do you know how many ambushes
I got over since potter Idris died?
Bayhoca was martyred in the ambush!
What are you talking about?
Both you and your daughter haven't
been friendly.
Both friendship and hostility have
a return.
If you had given me this ring at that time
Bayhoca wouldn't be under the dark soil now.
You carried this while I was looking
for the betrayer.
Osman Bey I cannot accept
your accusations!
Can we talk Osman Bey?
I'll see you later.
Now go away and think of the deaths
you and your father caused.
What kind of accusation is this,
Osman Bey? What are you trying to say?
What about you hiding things from me?
What did I hide from you?
No one except for that betrayer shall face
me today so you all can dodge my anger!
Bring me uncle Dündar.
Drag him if necessary.
He entered the khanqah my Bey.
Surround the khanqah.
Find him!
Let's go Alps!
Check upside.
He's gone my Bey.
- Search everywhere!
- Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
- Now!
- Let's go!
Look for him everywhere!
Do not let him escape.
Hurry up brothers!
Hurry up!
Find Dündar Bey!
Close the exits!
Search everywhere!
Hurry up Alps!
My Bey, we searched everywhere.
Dündar Bey is absent.
Osman Bey.
My Sheik, forgive me.
I left untimely.
And I had to search the khanqah.
This was not our desire, surely.
I understand your worries, Osman Bey.
Obviously, you found the betrayer
who ruined you.
Now it is time to make him pay, my Sheik.
Boran, stay here.
Goktug, come with me.
Alps, we are going!
Don't let anyone move!
Hold all the exist!
Go!
Let's go!
Who is that betrayer who made Osman
Bey that angry?
He figured out whose ring it is.
But he didn't tell me.
He doesn't want to announce before
he captures them.
Malhun, go to Kayı tent.
I don't think Osman Bey would want me
there, father.
Talk him through about why you
gave the ring to me.
Our reasons will make him angrier.
Yes, true but you'll learn
who the betrayer is.
Don't tire yourself up, my Bey. My men
will carry your clothes to your home.
- Come back again.
- Thank you.
Come back again.
I got excellent clothes from Konya,
for you to present your wife.
Come, I'll give you a discount, brother.
Have you seen Dündar Bey?
He was here recently, but he left to see
the families of martyred Alps.
Goodbye.
What is happening Petrus?
I didn't like how Boran Alp looked.
Dündar must be in trouble.
If Osman suspected something, that means
we're also in trouble.
What are we going to do?
Take precautions.
We have to learn what's happening.
You ordered us, Osman Bey.
Sit first.
This ring...
was presented to my uncle by my father.
Yes, it was Dündar Bey's first battle.
Your father take it our from his finger
and gave it to his brother.
The good old days.
Grandmother Halime told us.
What a battle it was!
Do you remember, brother?
Of course I do.
Grandmother Halime heard that uncle Dündar
was captured by the enemy in the war.
She told everyone while she cried.
Our hearts were shattered.
May they be in heaven inshallah.
- Amin.
- Amin, inshallah.
I wish...
my grandmother's tears
dried up...
I wish this ring of my father was a
rope wrapped on my uncle's neck!
What are you saying Osman Bey?
My uncle was...
a disappointment to my father.
He ripped our hearts out.
He was my grandmother's tears.
He scratched our eyes out!
He was my ancestors' breath!
He took our breath away!
All the Beys after my ancestor Oghuz
shall damn my Uncle!
Osman Bey what is it?
You would never curse.
Osman Bey, the unrest is within our
ancestors including your father now.
Osman Bey what is your tongue which shows
mercy all around the world saying?
I wish I was speechless so I wouldn't have
said what you just heard, Bamsı Bey.
Brother, we don't know what is happening.
Tell us.
The betrayer who was serving both to
Papa's dogs...
and infidel Nicola...
is my uncle Dundar Bey.
You...
What are you saying brother?
Are you saying that our uncle
caused my son's death?
This is a slander if
you don't have a proof.
Brother.
Uncle shot the arrow which killed
potter Idris.
This ring fell from his bloody finger.
He was afraid that Papa's spies
would talk.
Then he knows them too.
He was serving them too.
Uncle...
Dündar...
What am I going to do to you now?
I want revenge Osman Bey!
I want blood against my son's blood!
My valiant brother.
My mournful brother.
Do you think my uncle's dirty blood will
relieve my grandmother's, my ancestors',
my father's, our burning heart?
Tell me.
Brother.
Son.
- Bamsı Bey.
- Son.
Beys!
Pull yourself together!
Brother, what are we going to do?
How are we going to clean this dirt
on us, brother?
My Alps are searching for him in Sogut,
brother.
Once I got my uncle...
Once I got him...
But...
no one should know about this
for now.
Until that Dündar shows himself to us, our
swords shall remain in the scabbards.
This is what we have to do.
Do you understand?
Bury the shame...
Bury the pain in your hearts.
When he shows up, his blood will be
halal for our valiants!
What do you want Dündar Bey?
I have to see Lord Nicola right now!
You collaborated with the enemy ha?
I did! I collaborated with Geyhatu's dogs
as well, because it led us to victory!
Osman destroyed my army! Togay's soldiers
wiped out my remaining soldiers!
- Is this what you call a victory?
- That's alright!
Osman destroyed Togay's carrions!
Osman saved you from a trouble
that you'd not be able to get rid of.
Togay will return someday eventually.
What are we going to do then?
Are we going to fight Mongols?
Kalanoz.
Before Togay comes back, we'll
go forward for our aims.
Sogut.
What is this?
Papa's rats undermined Sogut.
I made Osman lose his dignity.
We'll enter Sogut through these tunnels...
and we'll get out with a victory.
This would be a golden victory, Nicola.
- Take it to Sogut.
- Okay Bala Hatun, don't worry.
Alaca, wait here.
What's now, Malhun Hatun?
Where are you going?
I'll see Osman Bey.
Osman Bey has a meeting with Kayı Beys.
Okay then, I'll wait.
Are you going to tell him your tradings
with Nicola?
Or has Umur Bey been captured and
we have to save him?
Bala Hatun, it's clear that you are not
here to chat.
If you want to fight, this is not the
right place.
I don't, Malhun Hatun I want to let you
understand you only brought us trouble.
We didn't bring trouble. We came
in a trouble.
Now we are working to get rid of
this trouble.
You should know that.
Osman Bey is available now, excuse me.
Of course, Malhun Hatun.
Can I come in Osman Bey?
Come.
Osman Bey, I am here because I respect
you being angry.
Listen to me this time.
You welcomed me, that's right.
I am grateful.
I should have brought the ring to you
as soon as I found it.
But, feel me, Osman Bey. I am responsible
for my tribe and my father.
I didn't want to act without
consulting him.
But Umur Bey decided on keeping this
ring as a secret, right?
He wanted you to show mercy if the
betrayer was one of your close ones.
A Bey doesn't discriminate!
The one who shows mercy to treason
betrays to the good ones!
But you wanted to find the betrayer
before Osman Bey, ha?
We would never give you this ring if
we wanted to ruin you Osman Bey.
Think of it.
Why is this Hatun here Osman Bey?
Malhun Hatun found this ring...
in the place where potter Idris died.
Did she hide it so far?
Bala Hatun.
Who was the man Osman Bey was trying
to make talk?
Idris. He was a potter.
So the betrayers are in your tent.
We were together Osman Bey.
She did this near me.
This is Uncle Dündar's ring.
Dündar Bey?
Ertugrul Bey's brother...
- Uncle Dündar's?
- Yes.
No one must know about this.
Hazal Hatun shouldn't hear this.
Of course my Osman.
Keep an eye on her.
Invite her to meal center tomorrow.
Hazal Hatun will lead us to uncle Dündar.
I'll keep an eye on her.
Don't you worry.
Sir, Dündar Bey is here.
Let him in.
Who is this Turk?
Uncle of the man who killed your brother.
- Is this Dündar?
- Ssshhh.
Hide your anger.
He is my trojan horse.
Dündar Bey...
as you dared to come here, it must
be about something very important.
Yes it is.
Osman learned I killed potter Idris.
What else did he learn?
Isn't that enough?
Does he know about Petrus?
Only me so far.
I have nowhere else to go Nicola.
Friends are for days
like these, Dündar Bey.
My castle is your home.
Thank you.
I want to take my wife Hazal
in the castle.
Dündar Bey.
You are a bit pale.
Relieve, sit.
Hazal Hatun will be my guest just like you
Dündar Bey. Don't worry.
How? Osman killed Kalanoz's army and
Togay's soldiers.
Dündar Bey, this is better.
Osman and I are now head to head.
No games anymore. We both will take
what we want.
You need to rest now.
Commander Mikiz!
Prepare Dündar Bey's room.
Let him rest.
What's it, Bala Hatun?
Are you here to quarrel?
I want to talk to you in private.
Aren't you sick of talking, Hatun?
Don't push it, Hatun.
I want to talk in private.
When did you start waylaying Hatun?
What is your problem?
You tricked me!
You kept the ring!
You talked about betrayers all the time.
You asked for proof while
you're hiding it!
I answered Osman Bey.
If you were to answer me instead of Osman Bey,
your arrogant head would've been cut off!
We are leaving!
Let's go!
Kayı Alp, how sweet you are!
But you are useless.
You are always sleeping.
How is my Alp sleeping?
Mashallah (praise be)
He is growing up.
You must have a problem, Hazal Hatun.
Dündar Bey...
hasn't returned.
He told me to set dinner but he is
still absent.
He didn't inform me either.
At least he used to inform you when
he was going to be absent.
He didn't even inform me!
You don't know where he is too.
Then I have to ask Osman Bey.
Where is my Alp's grandfather?
Hasn't he returned?
What are you doing now, father?
Osman Bey didn't speak of a name, ha?
Osman Bey is secretive.
He is blaming us for delivering the ring
lately instead of thanking us.
He is hurt.
He is right to be angry for a while.
But his actions take us to hostility.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come Bahadır.
We increased the number of Alps
around the tent, my Bey.
Okay.
Keep your eyes open.
Togay is like a snake.
You cannot predict what he'll do.
Don't worry my Bey.
What is it Malhun?
You seem sad.
Osman Bey doesn't trust us.
We did wrong to hide the ring, my Bey.
What happened happened.
Don't worry anymore.
Excuse me my Bey.
Okay, go.
Go rest, pull yourself together.
This girl is hiding something from me.
Let's hope for the best.
I was so offended to be infantilized,
so I waylaid her.
What was your goal Bala?
I wanted to call her to account
for what she did to us my Bey.
So you wanted to call her to account.
Can I come in Osman Bey?
Come.
What's it Hazal Hatun?
We haven't heard of Dündar.
This is not him.
Do you know anything Osman Bey?
Who can know what you don't know?
If you worry this lot...
then...
you know where Dündar Bey is.
I don't know, Osman Bey.
Why would I ask you if I knew?
So you don't know?
Hazal Hatun, come to the meal center
with me tomorrow.
I'll need help. Also you'd let yourself
a while.
Okay.
Sure, Bala Hatun.
We'll eventually
hear about him here in Sogut.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come.
She doesn't know where Dündar Bey is.
All she is worried about is the things
they did behind my back.
Tell me.
We investigated, my Bey.
No one saw Dündar Bey.
He is out of Sogut, apparently.
He won't get away from my wrath even
if he goes to the far end of the world!
Watch Dündar Bey's tent.
- Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
- Command is yours my Bey.
We'll talk about your issue later Bala.
Keep an eye on Hazal Hatun for now.
She'll lead us to my uncle.
Don't worry my Bey.
Excuse me.
From a sea to another.
This latter is for Papa.
Dündar's mask has fallen.
He went to Nicola.
Osman must have suspected him.
We are safe for now.
Hazal Hatun.
She is still a threat to us. Dündar must
have told her about us. Where is she?
She is in the tent, but if she had talked,
Osman would have found us by now.
We have to kill her before she speaks!
There's no another way.
May Allah bless you.
Enjoy your meal.
- May Allah bless you.
- Enjoy your meal.
May Allah bless you, daughter.
Mother Fatma, has your daughter Irmak
healed? Does she need anything?
She has food thanks to you Bala Hatun.
Her blood renewed.
May Allah bless you.
Masha Allah (praise be).
I will come to your house.
I'll salute Irmak.
Of course. You are most welcome.
Gonca, let's go to Mother Fatma's.
Let's go.
Wait a minute mother.
Hazal Hatun.
We are going Mother Fatma's.
Can you manage here?
Of course. I got it. You can go.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Ayse Hatun.
We are going to the bazaar to
buy cloth.
- Let's go.
- Okay my Hanım.
Osman Bey was right. Hazal Hatun was
waiting for us to leave.
Let Boran Alp know Gonca.
Go now.
Okay Bala.
Hazal Hatun is coming here.
- Is she alone?
- She is with a helper Hatun.
We can't kill her today.
It'll draw attention.
What are we going to do?
Where is my Dündar Bey?
Do you know?
We haven't seen him since yesterday.
I have quality clothes from Konya.
If you want to have a look...
Don't play with me Petrus.
I know who you are.
Where is my man, Dündar Bey?
What is happening?
What is happening in this sinister town?
Has anyone followed you on your
way here Hazal Hatun?
No.
What is happening?
Dündar Bey refuged to Nicola.
Osman.
How did he know?
We just got informed Hazal Hatun.
Osman is looking for
Dündar Bey everywhere.
He doesn't suspect you, obviously.
At least for now.
You didn't like this cloth.
Did he just leave me and run off?
Dündar Bey had a plan for a situation
lilke this?
Plan?
What kind of plan?
We are prepared. Don't worry.
Be calm.
- I can't go back to the tent.
- We'll take you to Dündar Bey.
Get rid of the Hatun with you and
come to Boztepe.
No, I have to go back to the tent.
I must take my goods, my ornament...
Never!
We don't have time for this. Osman will
chase you if he learns where Dündar is.
Now go.
Now.
We bury her.
No one will find her.
She is confused, apparently She's trying
to figure out what she's going to do.
What are you looking at Boran Alp?
Why are you surprised?
Let's go.
Where are Alps?
Aren't we returning to the meal center,
my Hanım?
You return to the tent.
I have things to do.
I'll inform Osman Bey.
Brother, follow her.
Let's go my Gonca, let's go.
This is enough to cover her sins.
What about Dündar?
Dündar is still a big threat for us.
His turn will come.
Come on. Let's leave.
What is this hole for?
Dündar Bey entrusted us gold and some
papers in case he runs off.
He told us to give them to you.
All in this hole.
This hole is empty.
What are you doing?
Everyone gets what they deserve!
Let me go.
Let me go!
Why are you doing this?
Your reason of death is betraying
your people.
Sir Petrus, shall I end her?
End her.
No!
Damn it! Osman!
Run Petrus!
I'd love to bury you alive,
you should thank to my Bey.
Get out.
You'll tell everything!
Being silent is the
biggest pray, Savcı Bey.
I know how to make you talk.
Are you working for Papa...
or Nicola dog?
Take him!
So you are the head of evil, huh?
Right?!
So, you are Petros, huh?
What about Süleyman that my
father mentioned?
Where is Melik the merchant?
Tell me!
They are decaying under the soil.
Now it's my turn.
Come on, kill me!
Kill me!
Petros, huh?
Petros...
You won't die that easy.
We'll have some conversations, Süleyman.
You can call me Petros.
Petros, huh?
Hazal Hatun of Çobanoğullar,
sister to a valiant brother.
Did you provoke my uncle
all this time?
Sooner or later...
...you will face your end, Osman Bey.
Take them away.
Osman Bey captured Hazal Hatun.
Let's greet them, Gonca.
What did they do?
O' people!
These are the low people who
worked with the traitors in our tribe!
Traitors! Burn in hell!
God damn you!
We caught Hazal Hatun running away
with them.
How can Hazal Hatun do that?
I found out who the traitor who
deceived many of our alps.
This is the darkest day of mine.
The traitor of our tribe is
someone from my own blood...
...my uncle Dündar Bey!
He will be caught soon and get
punished as he deserves.
Father...
What did you do...
Take Hazal Hatun to the tent.
And put guards at her tent.
She won't leave there before
my uncle Dündar get's captured.
And after he gets caught, send
her to her family.
She will never step into my lands
in my lifetime.
Come on.
Take these two to the caged tent.
Osman Bey.
I told you that...
...even if the traitor is
my father...
...his blood is halal for you.
Let it be as the laws say.
Let there be no traitor
left in our tribe.
Don't feel ashamed, Aygül.
Children can't suffer for their
fathers' sins.
You are a crown on our heads.
It is my uncle Dündar Bey who should
feel ashamed.
Brother...
Let us start from the beginning then.
You led the Cumans here to get documents.
And my uncle Dündar helped you, huh?
Why did you try to bury Hazal Hatun alive?
When Dündar's treachery got revealed, you
wanted to kill her who knows everything.
Right?
When Osman Bey questions,
you will answer.
Hazal Hatun knew that you serve the pope,
that you are allied with Nikola against me.
You were scared to get revealed,
didn't you?
If you know everything,
what do you want from us?
I want Dündar! Dündar!
Where is Dündar?
Where?
Why should I tell you this?
Why should I tell you where
your uncle...
...who cause the death of
Bayhoca...
...and...
...many of your alps for
your throne?
Why should I waste a useful
ally like him?
He will be a trouble for you and
the Turkish tribes as long as he is alive.
Why should I tell you where
a traitor hides, Osman Bey?
My question is simple, Petros.
Very simple.
You will stay alive until Dündar dies.
As long as he breathes,
you will want to die.
you will get tortured...
...you will want to die.
Now, tell me where Dündar is.
Where?
Petros, tell him.
Tell him...
Dündar Bey is over.
What good can his life do?
Osman Bey knows everything now.
We lost.
Let it end now.
I want to die, that's all. Tell him.
Nikola.
Dündar took refuge in Nikola.
Get out of my way.
You know Osman Bey's order, Aygül.
I'm the last person to run
over Osman Bey's orders, Cerkutay.
I have some things to say.
Don't waste time.
You did everything together, didn't you?
You are in treachery since the day that
my father couldn't be the bey.
It is your father who betrays,
not me.
Dündar Bey son of Süleyman Shah.
Your father.
A Kayı bey.
I'm of the Çobanoğulları.
I'm not a traitor.
You never felt that you belonged
to this tribe.
It is you who fed my father
with treason.
I've put effort for him to
act like a man...
...but it was her daughter
who acted like a man.
Not him.
My revenge for my mother
is coming, Hazal Hatun.
Don't think that it's over.
So?
What are you waiting for?
Get your revenge.
Thank Osman Bey.
If it wasn't for his order,
it would be your head falling.
Hazal Hatun.
I couldn't cut your throat...
...like I cut your mother's...
Aygül...
...that's why I'm sad.
We found out who is the murderer
of your brother, Ertuğrul.
It was Dündar Bey who caused
him to die in that ambush.
Shame on you Dündar Bey.
Shame on you.
Is it true, Savcı Bey?
It's true, my wife.
The traitor is my uncle.
Where is that traitor?
Where did he go to?
It's a matter of time to
find him.
For him to get caught and
die in my hands.
It's a matter of time.
You know best what you feel, Aygül.
I can't.
I don't even remember the faces of mine.
What does mother mean?
What does father mean?
I never knew.
I wish I never knew as well.
That sinister Hazal Hatun killed
my mother.
I live with her in this tribe for months.
Another person I live with
in this tribe...
...I mean...
...my father...
...will get killed by
Osman Bey.
For being a traitor.
You are right, Cerkutay.
I know best how I feel.
I'm with you.
I'll do anything to console you.
I know, you are mad at me.
Even though I don't know why.
But if you want to talk about it...
You understand me the best...
...Cerkutay.
May I enter, my bey?
Come.
-Any news?
-My bey.
We know who the traitor is.
Who is it?
Dündar Bey.
Dündar Bey, huh?
It was clear.
It was clear that someone who
enters Osman Bey's tent.
Where is Dündar Bey?
He isn't around, my bey.
Osman Bey and his alps are searching.
It seems that he is in hiding.
He must've taken refuge in whoever
he was working for.
You worked well, Bahadır.
Find out where Dündar Bey is.
Let me know at once if Osman Bey
captures him.
As you order, my bey.
Look at what Dündar Bey did...
Uncle!
My uncle is with Nikola.
From now on...
I know what's necessary to do.
We will send a messenger and we will
take my uncle from them...
in return for ransom money.
I want to go, Osman Bey.
You are angry now.
You are angry.
I don't want you to see Nikola and...
I don't want you to see my uncle.
What's best is...
that Gündüz brother should go.
This is better, brother.
Brother...
it's your responsibility.
We will give them everything they want.
However, not our lands.
They will want so many things, Osman Bey.
Goods or property don't matter.
I just want to get through this.
We will make everything up.
Savcı brother. Bayhoca's killer suffered
the consequences.
Now we know why.
He...
will pay for it.
Don't worry.
I will feel better, brother.
I will feel better.
However, when Nikola dies
too, I will be more comfortable.
- Inshallah.
I managed to step in Söğüt.
The tunnels shown on the map...
are real.
Petrus's shop, the church and the inn.
They are all connected.
I should confess
that I hated your tricks, Nikola.
Now, I see that you are going to win a
victory thanks to your political wisdom.
Söğüt is ours now.
No one will prevent that.
What's your plan, Nikola?
Gündüz Bey is here.
So, Osman knows Dündar Bey is here.
Let him in.
Gündüz Bey.
Where is Dündar Bey?
- What are you talking about?
- Stop playing with me.
I know that the traitor is here.
Listen to me carefully.
Give him to me.
Why would I give a loyal man like
Dündar Bey to you?
You're done with him, that's why.
He is someone disreputable now.
And...
he is a disgrace of Kayıs.
Osman dreams of a bloody end, obviously.
As every traitor has a bloody end.
So, Gündüz Bey...
what do you offer for Dündar Bey?
Ransom.
A thousand gold coins.
So...
this is my worth.
The traitor is here.
Traitor?
Osman...
treated me as if I'm nobody...
in the lands that I and my brother took.
He endangered everything we took.
He took possession of our tent.
He took my deserved Beyhood from me.
We are surrounded by
enemies because of him.
Your eyes are still closed, Gündüz.
Wake up, Gündüz!
If there's a traitor in
the tent, it's not me.
It's Osman.
Uncle.
When I looked at your eyes...
I used to see my father.
When I looked at your face...
I used to see the beautiful face of
my grandmother, Hayme Mother.
What did you do to yourself, uncle?
Tell me. What did you do to yourself?
How could you betray our
family and traditions?
How could you? Tell me, father!
How!
I protect my family and
traditions in my heart!
Don't worry.
I won't let Geyhatu take over these lands
that my brother Ertuğrul Ghazi took.
I won't let our Alps die...
because of Osman.
Bravo!
When I look at your face now...
Let me tell you what I think of when I
look at your ambitious eyes, uncle.
Tell me.
A miserable person.
A traitor...
who is ambitious and who is the reason
for our Alps' death.
That's enough.
It just hurts me to see...
the relatives hating each other.
My Alps will be waiting for
you next to the Castle...
with a thousand gold coins.
Think wisely, Nikola.
A thousand gold coins...
will be yours with just an order of yours.
I love generous offers.
Your offer made me happy but
Dündar Bey is my guest.
He will stay here as long as he wants.
The gold coins that Osman
will give can't buy...
the peace that Dündar Bey and
I set up here, Gündüz Bey.
So, I am not giving you Dündar Bey.
I send my regards to Osman Bey.
The day you die will be our feast day.
The day you
die will be our feast day, uncle!
Dündar Bey...
you should rest.
We will be in peace here soon.
Söğüt is already ours.
Dündar is a traitor. He doesn't
worth a gold coin.
Let Osman kill him.
Dündar doesn't have any power or dignity.
We'll see, Kalanoz.
We'll see.
Helen.
Go to Umur Bey and tell him
I want to meet him to talk about trade.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in, brother.
Tell me, brother.
Did you see my uncle?
Did you look into the traitor's eyes?
Tell me.
I did, brother.
He believes his own lie. He says
he will protect our tent from Geyhatu.
He makes up excuses for his betrayal.
What about Nikola?
Did he accept the ransom?
No.
He has another trick, obviously.
I'm sure he has.
However, he should think that we have
no other choice than ransom.
- He plays his trick according to that.
- Do we have another choice, Osman Bey?
We don't have any spies in the Castle.
We will get my uncle out of that Castle.
We will take him from Nikola
and bring him to the tent.
Umur Bey.
Osman prevented our trade.
However, he can't prevent our friendship.
I'm happy about that.
Osman is angry because he's desperate.
Only the Beys like you can discipline him.
We'll have peace by that.
He is angrier this time, Nikola.
He learned that
the traitor in the tent is Dündar Bey.
And Dündar escaped.
Who knows where he is hiding...
He took shelter in the lands
of trade and peace...
like you did, Umur Bey.
What?
- Is Dündar here?
- For now.
Other Turks hate him too as Osman does.
Then...
stop the hate.
- Send him to Osman.
- Umur Bey...
I can see that you're wise.
However, I am as wise as you.
I want to do something to stop the
hostility between me and Osman.
And I can give you power too
if I can do that.
What are you thinking, Nikola?
What happens if you give the traitor
to Osman?
When you give him to Osman...
he will think you are respected.
Just him? No.
All of the Beys will think the same.
And your dignity will be my
biggest power, Umur Bey.
What do you want in return for it?
Osman offered me a thousand gold coins.
If you offer me ten thousand gold coins...
I will give you Dündar.
So, the gold will be mine, the dignity
will be yours...
and his blood will be Osman's.
I will do everything I can.
I love good agreements.
You should join us for dinner.
İnegöl needs new goods.
We will talk again
when I come to take Dündar Bey.
However you want, Umur Bey.
However you want.
Dündar Bey.
A Turkmen Bey...
shouldn't take shelter in the
enemy's place.
Umur Bey, we have the same path.
- The peace and the trade.
- Don't.
Don't ever consider me equal to you!
I sell goods.
However, you sell your character.
Shame on you!
Don't criticize me!
Ever.
The lands that
you are at will be mine soon.
Don't forget.
When that time comes, I will be
against you.
I was with Nikola.
We had a trade situation.
I went to talk about it.
May Allah give you abundance, Umur Bey.
I...
saw Dündar Bey there.
Sadly, I learned that the thumb ring...
belonged to him.
Good for you, then.
Nikola wants ten thousand gold coins.
Osman Bey...
I can help if you want.
You want to help because you didn't give
me the thumb ring on time.
Don't worry, Umur Bey.
We will figure it out.
What about the friendship, Osman Bey?
Tell me what I should do to stop
the hostility between us.
- Do you want to be friends with us?
- Of course, Osman Bey.
You came here in vain, Umur Bey.
What you should do is...
to stay out of my business.
Now...
go to your tent.
Okay then, Osman Bey.
Okay then.
Baysungur.
Yes, my Bey.
Tell the Beys to come here.
The miners will get to Söğüt by
using these tunnels.
Will the Mongol fire blow out
at the same time?
In the mosque, in the inn...
and in the soup kitchen.
At the same time.
I can't even think of the panic.
Our union will come our of Petrus' shop
and will attack the Alps.
I will take the archers and
cavalries. Then, I will attack.
What about me?
You will meet the troop when Osman gets
out of his tent with the Alps...
and when the tent is left, you
will destroy there.
It was wise of you to accept the ransom.
It's the best excuse to stall Osman.
What about Dündar?
Dündar.
When we are done here...
you will be the person who
will kill him, Kalanoz.
Nikola...
is kidding with us or
he doesn't know how to count!
This can't be a ransom, Osman Bey.
He wants to weaken us.
If we pay what he wants, we can't
fulfill the needs of the tent...
...nor the expenditures of
the campaigns.
And he will use the heathen's money
to feed the soldiers he'll use against us.
He will surely do that, Davud Bey.
If so...
...if we can't give this ransom.
Then we know what to do.
We'll march to İnegöl and blow down
that castle upon Nikola and Dündar.
There is nothing else we can do,
Osman Bey.
My opinion about İnegöl Castle is
known, is it not?
It is. It is.
You think about sieging it.
Cutting its breath.
And you think that we need
more alps.
Otherwise, attacking the walls...
...will give no result, right?
Then, tell me how will we kill the
murderers of my son, Osman Bey!
Nikola...
...when he asked for Kulucahisar
for Bayhoca...
...remember what we said.
We remember it, Osman Bey.
Some of us said that the lands
of the country can't be given.
Some of us said that we should
save the Kayı bey.
And what did I do?
You saved Bayhoca.
And you didn't give our castle.
I will do the same now.
I will take Dündar apart from that
castle.
And I won't give a coin
to this dog called Nikola!
I was suspicious of Dündar Bey.
But I didn't expect this much.
May Allah save everyone from
such curse.
What will happen now, my bey?
Now...
...he has to pay the heavy ransom
that Nikola wants.
As long as his treacherous uncle
lives...
...he'll have no reputation among
the Turkmen tribes.
Osman Bey...
You look sad.
Isn't that much burden too much
for a man, father?
That's for Osman Bey to think.
We'll think about our own burden.
Osman Bey hoped for us to ease his burden.
He had hopes for us.
It's late, father.
Good night.
Is this the thing I feared?
Finally.
You will kill us now.
Our holy father in heaven...
I thought that...
...you will serve better...
...alive than dead.
Will you release us?
What do you want in return.
Dündar.
You will stay here.
You will go to İnegöl to meet with Nikola.
You will meet Dündar in secret.
And you will convince him to run away
to Constantinople.
You will bring him to me.
Even if I convince Nikola...
...how will I convince Dündar Bey?
I will let you know...
...what to tell Nikola and Dündar.
Me...
...what will you do to me.
If I get what I want.
I will send you to the pope.
And you will carry a letter from me.
But...
...if you fail...
...I will personally send Petros'
head to the pope.
We trust your word.
If that's your offer.
We are listening, Osman Bey.
Good.
Listen well, then.
Nikola...
So, Dündar Bey took refuge
under you.
That was the best he could.
Only his enemy can open his arms
to a traitor, right?
Unfortunately, our most loyal spy
won't work now.
We won't need him.
When I take Söğüt, all the Turkish
hegemony in Bhytinia will end.
It will be the end of Osman, Simon.
It will be.
Then, I should go and talk to Dündar.
I wonder what will be the last crumbs
of information I will get from him.
Where is Petros?
He went to İznik to see the pope's helper.
He'll be back in a few day.
If you allow me, Lord Nikola.
I heard what happened, Dündar Bey.
Have you got any news from Hazal?
Unfortunately. We have more important
problems than Hazal Hatun now.
What happened to Hazal, I said!
Osman Bey banished Hazal Hatun
from the tribe.
He sent her to his brother.
Oh, Hazal.
Don't worry.
When we take you to Constantinople,
Hazal Hatun will come with us.
Petros arranged everything.
What does that mean?
I will stay here and fight for the
throne that I deserve.
Or, did you discard me?
Not us, Dündar Bey.
It is Nikola who discarded you.
What does that mean?
Nikola accepted the ransom that
Osman will pay for you.
This isn't possible.
It's not.
If you had heard the price that Osman
is willing to pay for you.
You would know that it's possible.
But it doesn't fit you to be daunted,
Dündar Bey.
We still need each other.
Even if Nikola betrays you for a bunch of
golds that Osman offers.
I will kill him!
I will kill him! I will kill him!
No. I can't get you out of
here if you do that.
Why are you endangering yourself for me?
If Nikola gives you to Osman...
it will be our end too.
And we still need a powerful
Bey like you...
for Papa's aims on these lands.
How will you get me out of here?
Listen to me carefully.
Do you need anything else?
No.
I was granted to be exiled from the
lands...
that I and my brother took.
Uncle!
You won't even have a grave...
in those lands that my father took.
I won't even give you any land
that you will rot in!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com